In the major web browsers like Firefox or Chrome,
you can actually see the messages and files
getting transmitted between you and the server.
In Chrome, go to the View menu,
then select Developer, and Developer tools.
That's what I have open here.
Then click up here on the Network tab and visit a website.
I'm going to visit the Udacity homepage.
So, these are all the files that your browser requests when going to a web page.
If you click on a file, for example, here,
you'll see Request Method: GET,
which is your browser saying,
"Get me this file or information from the server."
The reason I'm showing you all of this is so that you can
physically see how the web actually works and what is going on.
As you practice coding with Flask,
it can be helpful to understand the basics of how
the Internet works between a browser and a server.